pac-revenue-share.com 2009-07-19

# PremiumAdsClub Revenue Share : Privacy Policy

**THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT DISCLOSES THE PRIVACY PRACTICES FOR PAC REVENUE SHARE**  
Information Collection and Use of Information In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give his contact information (email address).

This information is used to contact the member about the service and products we provide or wish to provide. We will not sell, share, or rent personal information to others.

**SECURITY**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our member's personal information. When a memberr submits sensitive information via our site, the information is protected both online and off-line. Only the administrator of this site can access personal information of the members.

**CORRECTION**  
Updating Personal Information If a user's personally identifiable information changes, we provide a way to correct that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done within the member area.

**RIGHT TO CANCEL**  
Our members can cancel their membership and be removed from all newsletters and databases. To do this, send a ticket to the admin with the subject CANCEL ACCOUNT. Know that no refunds will be issued should a member decide to cancel his/her account.

**SITE AND SERVICE UPDATES**  
We may send the member site and service announcement updates. We communicate with the members to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their accounts via email.

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**  
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will notify users by way of an email. Members will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.
